hairmixer.com 2018-06-14

# Privacy Policy

Modiface Inc. believes that your personal information deserves protection and we subscribe to the privacy principles set out in the Government of Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. This privacy policy describes our practices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your personal information. By using our website you consent and agree to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information and to the privacy practices set out in this policy. Modiface expressly reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time.

**General Statistics**

We may use personal information and data collected through your emails and use of our website to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use and for sharing with our affiliates and advertisers. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any information that could identify you personally.

**How do we collect and use personal information?**

Modiface is in the business of face visualizations and face processing. As part of providing this service, we collect personal information from our users in a number of ways.

Unregistered Users

Your images and internet protocol (IP) address will be saved on our servers for a maximum of 24 hours for visualization purposes. They are deleted permanently with the 24 hours following the submission of your image(s).

Registered Users

In order to get access to certain services or applications through our website, you need to create a user account by submitting a user name and password and filling in our registration form. 

The information you provide during the registration process, such as your name, email, and/or face picture, will be stored on our servers permanently as long as your account is active.

We also collect some anonymous (non-personal) information from visitors to our website through the use of cookies. Cookies are used on most websites. They are text files with a unique identification number that are transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer. Cookies are only used to identify your computer but they do not save any personal information about you such as your name or address. Most browsers can be set up to accept or reject cookies, or simply notify you each time a cookie is set by a website you visit. We currently use cookies for measuring traffic statistics on our website and saving your information so you don't have to re-enter it on future visits when posting comments or participating in forums. We may also use cookies to provide personalized services to you, such as customized web pages and advertisements.

**How do we protect your personal information?**

We collect your personal information onto servers hosted by a reputable third party website hosting company and are restricted access servers. If you wish to obtain further information about our hosting company and its security measures, please email info@modiface.com.

**With whom do we share your personal information?**

We may disclose personal information to our agents, suppliers and service providers as part of making available our website and related products and services. All such persons and entities are provided only with the information needed to perform their specific function and may not use such information for other purposes. They are also bound by contract to maintain the confidentiality and security of personal information and are restricted from using such information in any way not expressly authorized by Modiface. ****

**What other organizations collect information?**

Advertisers

Our advertisers may collect information such as your internet protocol (IP) address, your geographic location, as well as other information deemed important in selecting the type and style of advertisements to run.

## Exceptions

We reserve the right to use and disclose personal information to comply with applicable laws and regulations and local, provincial and national governmental requests, to operate our websites properly, or to protect the rights and property of Modiface and its users, sponsors, providers, or licensors.

For questions or concerns regarding your personal information and our privacy policy, or to update, correct or delete your personal information, please contact:

Attention: Modiface Privacy Department

Modiface Inc.

7 St. Thomas Street, Unit 502 Toronto, Ontario, Canada, M5S 2B7 

info@modiface.com
